Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Records Concerning Events and Exhibitions
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Architecture, Yale University, records concerning events and exhibitions
1965-2017
RU 886
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
211.67
109 boxes
35141.6
The records consist of posters, programs, brochures, videorecordings, and photographic images (print and digital) documenting events and exhibits sponsored by the Yale School of Architecture.
Yale University. School of Architecture
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 19-H (YRG 19-H), Audio-visual materials and memorabilia documenting the Yale School of Architecture.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Copies of commercially produced audiovisual materials contained in this collection cannot be made for researcher use outside of the repository.
Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of posters, programs, brochures, videorecordings, and photographic images (print and digital) documenting events and exhibits sponsored by the Yale School of Architecture.
Exhibitions; Schools of architecture; Brochures; Born digital; Photographs; Posters; Programs; Yale University. School of Architecture
- Posters from events and exhibitions, circa 2000-2003; Accession 19ND-A-426
  - Posters from events and exhibitions, circa 2000-2003 (Folder 1)
- School of Architecture exhibit material, 1999-2001; Accession 2002-A-047
  - Catalogs
    - Spring 2001
      - 2 views of Eero Saarinen, 2001 (Box 1)
      - Architecture or Revolution, 2001 (Box 1)
      - Koetter Kim and Associates, 2001 (Box 1)
      - Saving Corporate Modernism, 2001 (Box 1)
    - 2000 Fall
      - Cesar Pelli, 2000 (Box 1)
    - 1999 Fall
      - Work of Daniel Libeskind, 1999 (Box 1)
      - Re-Connections: The work of the Eames Office, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Announcements of Exhibitions (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Open House Handout November Poster, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
    - Invitation to AIA Convention, 2000 May (Box 1)
    - Invitation to AIA Convention, 2001 May (Box 1)
  - Lecture Series Posters
    - Spring 2001 (Folder 2)
    - Fall 2000 (Folder 2)
    - Spring 2000 (Folder 2)
    - Fall 1999 (Folder 2)
    - Spring 1999 (Folder 2)
  - Posters of Symposiums
    - Corporate Modernism, 2001 Spring (Folder 2)
    - Next Cities, 2000 Fall (Folder 2)
    - Perspecta, 2000 Spring (Folder 2)
    - Constructs, 1999 Fall (Folder 2)
    - Open House, 2000 November (Folder 2)
  - Videorecordings
    - "Back to the Garden: Corporate Modernism in Context,", 2001; videotape (VHS) (Box 3)
- Records from the catalog for the exhibition of Paul Rudolph's Art and Architecture building, 1988; Accession 2002-A-145
  - Records from the catalog for the exhibition of Paul Rudolph's Art and Architecture building, 1988 (Box 1)
- Catalog and related materials for Tokyo segment of "Raising New Ground" exhibition, 2002; Accession 2003-A-052
  - Catalog and related materials for Tokyo segment of "Raising New Ground" exhibition, 2002 (Box 1)
- Photographs of the Eisenman/Krier and Tod Williams/Billie Tsien exhibits, 2003; Accession 2003-A-108
  - Photographs of the Eisenman/Krier and Tod Williams/Billie Tsien exhibits, 2003 (Box 1)
- Exhibit posters, postcards, and brochures, 2002; Accession 2003-A-110
  - Exhibit posters, postcards, and brochures, 2002 (Box 1)
- Exhibit postcards, programs, and posters from exhibits, 2003; Accession 2003-A-158
  - Exhibit postcards, programs, and posters from exhibits, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Digital images from the exhibit "Future Now, Year End Exhibition of Student Work," [computer files], 2003; Accession 2003-A-164 (Box 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
  - Future Now, Year End Exhibition of Student Work exhibition, 38 computer files, 2003
    General note
    Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
- Photographs of the exhibits "New Blue: Recent work of graduates of Yale School of Architecture, 1978-1998," and "Zaha Hadid Laboratory", 2001-2002; Accession 2003-A-165
  - Photographs of the exhibits "New Blue: Recent work of graduates of Yale School of Architecture, 1978-1998," and "Zaha Hadid Laboratory", 2001-2002 (Box 1)
- Exhibit panels from "New Blue: Recent Works of Graduates of the Yale School of Architecture", 2001; Accession 2004-A-029
  Scope and Contents
  The panels, each 44x44", are arranged by panel number.
  - 1. Audrey Matlock (1979), Armstrong World Industries Conference Center, Lancaster, PA, 1999; Audrey Matlock Architect, (amARCH), NY, NY, 2001 (Box 15)
  - 2. Alexander Gorlin (1980), House in the Rocky Mountains, Genesee, Colorado, 1998. Alexander Gorlin Architect, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 30)
  - 3. Jacob D. Albert (1980), Albert House, Cambridge, MA, 1993. Albert, Righter and Tittmann Architects, Inc. Boston, MA, 2001 (Box 4)
  - 4. Brian Healy (1981), Beach House, Long Beach Island, NJ, 1996. Brian Healy Architects, Boston, MA, 2001 (Box 10)
  - 5. Cameron Armstrong (1981), Armstrong-James House, Houston, Texas, 1993. photograph by Lisa Hester and Paul Hardaway. Cameron Armstrong Architects, Houston, TX, 2001 (Box 13)
  - 6. Eric Haesloop (1981), Long Meadow Ranch Winery, St. Helena, CA, 1998. Turnbull Griffin Haesloop, Berkeley, CA, 2001 (Box 34)
  - 7. Michael Cadwell (1981), Gatehouse, Long Island, NY, 1988. Cadwell and Murphy, Architects, Columbus, OH, 2001 (Box 6)
  - 8. Daniel Rowen/Frank Lupo (1981/'83), White Apartment, NY, 1995. Formerly New York Architects; Perkins and Will, Daniel Rowen Architect, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 1)
  - 9. Ted Mahl (1982), Independent Theoretical Drawings. RMW Architecture and Interiors, San Francisco, CA, 2001 (Box 36)
  - 10. Thomas A. Kligerman (1982), Marsh Residence, Upper Brookville, NY, 1995. photograph by Peter Aaron/Esto. Ike Kligerman Barkley Architects, P.C., NY, NY, 2001 (Box 37)
  - 11. Philip Parker (1983), Crossings Golf Course and Steel Works, Cincinnati, OH, 1999. Philip Parker Architect, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 11)
  - 12. Charles D. Dilworth (1983), Silicon Graphics North Charleston Site, Mountain View, CA, 1997. photograph by Steve Whittaker, STUDIOS Architecture, San Francisco, CA, 2001 (Box 31)
  - 13. Robert Taylor (1983)/Carol Burns (1983), Founders' Hall, Grace and Holy Trinity Cathedral, Kansas City, Missouri, 1999 photograph by Timothy Hursley Taylor and Burns Architects, Boston, MA, 2001 (Box 19)
  - 14. Jacques Richter (1983)/Ignacio Dahl Rocha ('83), Nestle Headquarters Renovation, Vevey, Switzerland, 2000. Richter et Dahl Rocha Bureau d'architectes, Lausanne, Switzerland, 2001 (Box 20)
  - 15. Marion Weiss (1983), Richter et Dahl Rocha Bureau d'architectes, Lausanne, Switzerland. Weiss/Manfredi Architects, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 16)
  - 16. Scott Merrill (1984), Seaside Chapel, Seaside, FL, 2001. Merrill and Pastor Architects, Vero Beach, FL (Box 33)
  - 17. Ted Trussell Porter (1984), Garden for Living, Sag Harbor, NY, 2001. Ryall Porter Architects, NY, NY (Box 27)
  - 18. John B. Tittman (1986), Tittmann House, Cambridge, MA, 1998. Albert, Righter and Tittmann Architects, Inc., Boston, MA, 2001 (Box 24)
  - 19. Lise Anne Couture (1986), NYSE Command Center and Virtual Trading Floor, NY, NY, 1999. Asymptote Architecture, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 17)
  - 20. Jeff Miles (1986), Ozone Maker, Project, 1994. Jeff Miles Architects and Polshek Partnership Architects, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 7)
  - 21. Maya Lin (1986), Langston Hughes Library, Clinton, TN, 1999. Maya Lin Studio, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 32)
  - 22. Soo K. Chan (1987), Coronation Road West House, Singapore, 2000. Coronation Road West House, Singapore, 2000., 2001 (Box 14)
  - 23. Gilbert. P. Schafer III (1988), New Residence, Palm Beach, FL, 1998. G.P. Schafer Architect, PLLC, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 21)
  - 24. Andrew Berman (1988), Center for Architecture, NY Chapter AIA Headquarters, NY, NY, current project. Andrew Berman Architect, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 26)
  - 25. Victor Deupi (1989), Proposal for Poundbury Development, Dorchester, England, 1998. Deupi Economakis, South Bend, Indiana., 2001 (Box 5)
  - 26. Koichi Yasuda (1989), Sakuradamon Police Box, Tokyo, Japan, 1993. Nikken Sekkei Ltd., Tokyo, Japan., 2001 (Box 3)
  - 27. Marc L'Italien (1990), "Habitat Africa! The Forest," Brookfield Zoo, Brookfield, IL, 2000, photograph by Doug Snower. EHDD Architecture (Esherick Homsey Dodge and Davis), Chicago, IL., 2001 (Box 28)
  - 28. Constance Adams (1990), Transhab Crew Quarters, 1999, synthesis.international and Lockheed Martin Space Operations Company, Houston, TX., 2001 (Box 23)
  - 29. Benedict O'Looney (1992), Duisburg Maritime Centre, Duisburg, Germany, 2000. Nicholas Grimshaw and Partners, London, England, 2001 (Box 22)
  - 30. Timothy Durfee (1992), "Made in California" exhibit, Los Angeles, CA, 2000. Durfee Regn Sandhaus and D/R: Design Research, Los Angeles, California, 2001 (Box 18)
  - 31. Charles Lazor (1993), Chicago 8 Box Storage Unit, 1997, photograph by Charles Lazor Blu Dot, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 2001 (Box 29)
  - 32. Scott Specht (1993)/Louise Harpman (1993), Concrete, Inc., NY, NY, 2000 Specht, Harpman, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 9)
  - 33. Michael Haverland (1994), Addition to the Timothy Dwight Elementary School, New Haven, CT, 2001, photograph by Andrew Bordwin. Michael Haverland Architects and Yale Urban Design Workshop, New Haven, CT (Box 25)
  - 34. Granger Moorhead (1995), Felt Stool No. 7, 2000. Moorhead and Moorhead, NY, NY, 2001 (Box 2)
  - 35. Hemant Jha (1998), Phonograph 1, 1999. hela design, New Haven, CT, 2001 (Box 12)
  - 36. Patricia Patkau (1978), Strawberry Vale Elementary School, Victoria, British Columbia, 1996. photograph by J. Dow. Patkau Architects Inc., Vancouver, British Columbia, 2001 (Box 35)
  - 37. Doug Garofalo (1987), Markow Residence, Prospect Heights, Illinois, 1999. 1999 photograph by William Kildow. Garofalo Architects, Chicago, Illinois., 2001 (Box 8)
- Exhibit posters from the student year-end show, 2003; Accession 2004-A-030
  - Marcus Carter #3, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Jennifer Silbert #12, 2003 (Box 1)
  - April Clark #5, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Ioana Barac / David Paz #1, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Yat Lun Ng #10, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Winy Maas Studio #11, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Marshall Bell #2, 2003 (Box 1)
  - William Tims #14, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Andrew Moddrell #9, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Christopher Marcinkoski #8, 2003 (Box 1)
  - Hanson Liu #6, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Ji-wook Chang #4, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Hanson Liu #7, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Greg Sobotka #13, 2003 (Folder 3)
  - Graduate Posters #1-4, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Graduate Poster #5, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Studio/Student work posters #1-2, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Undergraduate posters, 2003 (Box 5)
- Posters, calendars and brochures of events and activities sponsored by the School of Architecture, circa 1970-1987; Accession 2004-A-031
  Arranged by topic.
  - Posters and calendars (oversize), circa 1970-1987 (Folder 1)
  - Brochures
    - Masters of Architecture Graduation Exhibition, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Urban Fragments, 1985 (Box 2)
    - The Chairs of Frank Lloyd Wright, 1987 (Box 2)
- Images of exhibits "Intricacy" and "Rome" in the Art and Architecture Building, 2003; Accession 2004-A-096
  Requires written permission of the author or copyright holder to copy.
  - Images of exhibit "Intricacy" in the Art and Architecture Building, 2003; 19 (Box 2)
  - Images of exhibit "Rome" in the Art and Architecture Building, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Color transparencies (Box 1)
- Posters, postcards, and brochures from exhibits, 2003; Accession 2004-A-110
  - Posters, postcards, and brochures from exhibits, 2003 (Box 1)
- Student designed posters for Halloween, 2003; Accession 2004-A-111
  - Student designed posters for Halloween, 2003 (Box 1)
- Exhibit materials from "Robert Damora: 70 Years of Total Architecture", 2003-2004; Accession 2004-A-129
  - Art and Architecture Building (Paul Rudolph)
    - Exterior - view from Art Gallery; A-25, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - Exterior - York St. looking up; A-26, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - Exterior; A-27, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - Exterior - windows; A-28, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - Interior - 3rd floor near Dean's office; A-29, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - Interior - stairwell; A-30, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - 3rd floor wall/cu; A-31, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - Interior - textured detail; A-32, 1963 (Folder 1)
    - Exterior; A-19, 1963 (Folder 2)
    - Exterior - entire building; A-20, 1963 (Folder 2)
    - Interior- 3rd floor gate; A-21, 1963 (Folder 2)
    - Interior - shell in wall; A-22, 1963 (Folder 2)
    - Exterior - roof; A-23, 1963 (Folder 2)
    - Exterior - front entrance; A-24, 1963 (Folder 2)
  - General Motors Technical Center(Eero Saarinen) (Folder 2)
    - Exterior - red brick wall; B-7, 1965 (Folder 3C)
    - Exterior - blue brick wall; B-9, 1965 (Folder 3C)
    - Interior - stairs; B-18, 1965 (Folder 3A)
    - Interior - stairs with blue brick; B-21, 1965 (Folder 3D)
    - Interior - table colored chairs; B-23, 1965 (Folder 3B)
    - Interior - red flip flops and chairs; B-30, 1965 (Folder 3B)
    - Interior - curved glass wall; B-32, 1965 (Folder 3A)
    - Interior -round ceiling light; B-35, 1965 (Folder 3D)
    - Exterior - red brick wall with black smoke stack; B-3, 1965 (Folder 4)
    - Exterior - red brick wall; B-10, 1965 (Folder 4)
    - Interior - stairs; B-14, 1965 (Folder 4)
    - Interior - with red chairs; B-24, 1965 (Folder 4)
    - Interior - with pink doors and car; B-26, 1965 (Folder 4)
    - Interior - marble squares/bench; B-36, 1965 (Folder 4)
    - Exterior; B-4, 1965 (Folder 5A)
    - Exterior - blue/orange brick walls; B-6, 1965 (Folder 5A)
    - Interior - circular with wires; B-16, 1965 (Folder 5B)
    - Interior - pink and black doors; B-25, 1965 (Folder 5B)
  - Skyscraper - cross section - construction; C-02, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
  - Stadium
    - model-parking lot; C-6, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
    - section drawing; C-7, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
    - cross section drawing; C-8, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
  - Skyscraper - building section; C-01, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
  - Airport-quarter plan of airport; C-15, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
  - Municipal Tower
    - drawing; C-20, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
    - model; C-22, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
    - drawing; C-24, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
  - Playground
    - boy on tree thing; C-34, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
    - clay people; C-36, 1956-1958 (Folder 6)
  - Sprayed Concrete House
    - Aerial-carand person; C-2, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
    - house clay figures; C-3, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
  - Helix Apartment
    - drawing; C-11, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
    - montage; C-12, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
  - Municipal Tower
    - drawing; C-19, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
    - structural section; C-21, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
    - model/rooftop; C-23, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
    - man on stairs; C-25, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
    - round staircase; C-26, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
  - Playground
    - wading pool; C-32, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
    - clay people; C-33, 1956-1958 (Folder 7)
  - Airport - model-plane in sky; C-14, 1956-1958 (Folder 8)
  - Stadium-model-Exterior; C-5, 1956-1958 (Folder 8)
  - Helix Apt. - model-1 tower; C-10, 1956-1958 (Folder 8)
  - Bridge
    - street model; C-29, 1956-1958 (Folder 8)
    - model section view; C-30, 1956-1958 (Folder 8)
  - Community Common; D-10, undated (Folder 9)
  - model; D-11, undated (Folder 9)
  - ext - man near rouno date structures; D-12, undated (Folder 9)
  - House - 'Prefabricated Parts Permits Custom Planning'; D-20, undated (Folder 9)
  - Cross Section; D-21, undated (Folder 9)
  - Cape House
    - Interior - red carpet/kitchen table; D-23, undated (Folder 9)
    - model; D-27a, undated (Folder 9)
    - Interior - bathroom; D-24, undated (Folder 9)
    - D-32, undated (Folder 9)
    - model; D-33, undated (Folder 9)
  - Record Houses article - mid-May issue; D-37, undated (Folder 9)
  - Airplane Hangar - The Plan; D-27, undated (Folder 9)
  - Project Conclusion; D-3, undated (Folder 10)
  - Bahama House; D-5, undated (Folder 10)
  - Magazine cover - 'Architectural Record of 1962'; D-8 (Folder 10)
  - Cape House
    - wall framing system; D-19, undated (Folder 10)
    - Exterior; D-22, undated (Folder 10)
  - section drawing; D-24a, undated (Folder 10)
  - Berkshire House; D-27b, undated (Folder 10)
  - Airplane Hangar
    - The Plan; D-30, undated (Folder 10)
    - The Structure; D-2, undated (Folder 11)
    - The Hangar Doors; D-4, undated (Folder 11)
  - Bahama House
    - Sign; D-7, undated (Folder 11)
    - Section; D-9, undated (Folder 11)
  - Cape House - Exterior porch; D-24b, undated (Folder 11)
  - Berkshire House; D-29, undated (Folder 11)
  - Cape House; D-16, undated (Folder 12)
  - The Irving Room; D-17, undated (Folder 12)
  - Bahama House
    - drawing; D-34, undated (Folder 12)
    - construction sequence; D-35, undated (Folder 12)
    - roof plan; D-36, undated (Folder 12)
  - Berkshire House; D-28, undated (Folder 12)
  - Damora Credits; T-1, undated (Folder 12)
  - Biographic Notes; T-2, undated (Folder 12)
  - Architectural Photography Medal; T-3, undated (Folder 12)
  - The 48-Hour House; T-4, undated (Folder 12)
  - Concrete Skyscraper; T-5, undated (Folder 12)
  - A Concept of Natural Growth; T-7, undated (Folder 12)
  - A City Tower; T-8, undated (Folder 12)
  - Airport Planning; T-9, undated (Folder 12)
  - Hancock Building
    - Exterior closer view; E-2, 1977 (Folder 13A)
    - Exterior rouno date frame; E-5, 1977 (Folder 13B)
    - Exterior; E-7, 1977 (Folder 13A)
  - KNOLL; E-10, 1951 (Folder 13A)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA)
    - Exterior columns; E-13, 1939 (Folder 13B)
    - Exterior sculpture; E-14, 1939 (Folder 13C)
  - Rockefeller House - interior - living room; E-16, 1950 (Folder 13C)
  - Kleinhaus -Exterior; E-24, 1941 (Folder 13B)
  - Large K; E-9, 1951 (Folder 14A)
  - MoMA - Interior auditorium; E-12, 1939 (Folder 14D)
  - Rockefeller House - interior fireplace; E-17, 1950 (Folder 14A)
  - Kleinhans
    - exterior; E-20, 1941 (Folder 14B)
    - exterior; E-21, 1941 (Folder 14C)
    - interior stairs and curves; E-22, 1941 (Folder 14C)
    - interior stairs and curves; E-23, 1941 (Folder 14B)
  - Taylor House -concrete roof with 2 kids; F-9, 1962 (Folder 15)
  - Breuer House
    - Interior fireplace; F-18, 1948 (Folder 15)
    - interior - fireplace in foregrouno date; F-21, 1948 (Folder 15)
    - Exterior wooden porch; F-22b, 1948 (Folder 15)
  - Gropius House (Walter Gropius)
    - Exterior porch/cars in back; F-22, 1946 (Folder 15)
    - Interior home office; F-30, 1946 (Folder 15)
    - interior reflection of trees; F-32, 1946 (Folder 15)
    - interior glass house; F-33, 1946 (Folder 15)
  - Taylor House
    - Exterior car; F-4, 1962 (Folder 16)
    - Exterior columns, wicker; F-6, 1962 (Folder 16)
    - Exterior rooftop; F-7, 1962 (Folder 16)
    - Interior with 2 columns; F-8, 1962 (Folder 16)
  - Tower House - Exterior porch; F-14, 1960 (Folder 16)
  - Robinson House - ext tree in foregrouno date; F-15, 1948 (Folder 16)
  - Gropius House - ext spiral staircase; F-28, 1946 (Folder 16)
  - Taylor House - Exterior car; F-5, 1962 (Folder 17)
  - Breuer House
    - Exterior; F-19, 1948 (Folder 17)
    - Exterior; F-20, 1948 (Folder 17)
  - Gropius House (Walter Gropius)
    - Exterior - house with trellis; F-25, 1946 (Folder 17)
    - Exterior; F-26, 1946 (Folder 17)
    - Interior fireplace; F-27, 1946 (Folder 17)
  - Oversize exhibit panels
    - Art and Architecture Building with Paul Rudolph portrait; A-1 (digitized for preservation purposes), 1963; computer file (TIFF)
    - General Motors Technical Center (Eero Saarinen) (digitized for preservation purposes), computer file (TIFF)
      - Red wall and water tower; B-37 (digitized for preservation purposes), 1965; computer file (TIFF)
      - Interior stairs; B-38 (digitized for preservation purposes), 1965; computer file (TIFF)
    - Skyscraper; C-0 (digitized for preservation purposes), 1956-1958; computer file (TIFF)
    - Bridge model; C-27 (digitized for preservation purposes), 1956-1958; computer file (TIFF)
    - Cape house- Interior; D-14 (digitized for preservation purposes), undated; computer file (TIFF)
    - Knoll showroom- Interior; E-8 (digitized for preservation purposes), 1951; computer file (TIFF)
    - Gropius house-int-stairs; F-23 (digitized for preservation purposes), 1946; computer file (TIFF)
    - CBS building; L-1 (digitized for preservation purposes), 1966; computer file (TIFF)
    - Figure; L-3 (digitized for preservation purposes), undated; computer file (TIFF)
  - Color Transparencies of exhibit, undated (Box 18)
  - Exhibit images, 2003-2004; 16 (Box 19–20)
- Images from exhibits, 2001; Accession 2004-A-157
  Arranged chronologically.
  - "Saving Corporate Modernism: Assessing Three Landmark Buildings Designed by Gordon Bunshaft of Skidmore and Merrill", 2001 January 8 - March 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "WORKPLACE- The Work of the Office of Deborah Berke, Architect", 2001 February 12 - April 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Koetter Kim and Assoc.- Cities and Buildings", 2001 March 19 - May 4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Two Views of Eero Saarinen: The Architectural Photography of Balthazar Korab and Ezra Stoller", 2001 April 9 - May 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Fast Forward, Year End Exhibit of Student Work", 2001 May 18 - June 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Posters, programs, and invitations, 2004 Spring; Accession 2004-A-206
  - Posters, programs, and invitations, 2004 Spring (Box 1)
- Digital images of the exhibit "Big and Green: Toward Sustainable Architecture in the 21st Century"[computer files], 2004; Accession 2005-A-046 (Box 1–2)
  - Digital images of the exhibit "Big and Green: Toward Sustainable Architecture in the 21st Century", 2004; 41
- Images of the exhibit "Next Wave: Year End Student Work", 2004; Accession 2005-A-047
  - Images of the exhibit "Next Wave: Year End Student Work", 2004 (Box 1)
  - Computer files (Box 2–3)
- Images documenting the exhibit "PSFS: Nothing More Modern", 2004; Accession 2005-A-085
  - Color transparencies (4x5) documenting the exhibit "PSFS: Nothing More Modern,", 2004 (Box 1)
  - Digital images documenting the exhibit "PSFS: Nothing More Modern,", 2004; 22 computer files (TIFF) (Box 2–3)
- Images documenting the exhibit "Cesar Pelli, Building Designs 1965-2000", Accession 2005-A-088
  - Images documenting the exhibit "Cesar Pelli, Building Designs 1965-2000" (Box 1)
- Images of the exhibition "Light Structures - The work of Jorge Schlaich and Rudolf Bergermann", 2004-2005; Accession 2005-A-099
  - 15 color transparencies (4x5) of the exhibition "Light Structures - The work of Jorge Schlaich and Rudolf Bergermann,", 2004-2005 (Box 1)
  - Digital images of the exhibition "Light Structures - The work of Jorge Schlaich and Rudolf Bergermann,", 2004-2005; 16 computer files (TIFF) (Box 2)